bankfab.com 2017-02-09

# Privacy Policies :: First United Bank

Consumer Privacy Policy

Online Privacy Policy

Social Media Policy

### Consumer Privacy Policy

Printer Friendly Version with Opt-Out Form

###### FACTS

| 

###### WHAT DOES FIRST UNITED DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
  
---|---  
  
###### Why?

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
###### What?

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and Credit History
  * Account Balances and Payment History
  * Transaction History and Account Transactions

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
###### How?

| 

All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons First United chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
###### REASONS WE CAN SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

| 

##### Does First United share?

| 

##### Can you limit this sharing?  
  
---|---|---  
  
**For our everyday business purposes -** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes -** to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -** information about your transactions and experiences

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -** information about your creditworthiness

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
###### To limit our sharing

| 

Print out and mail this form: Printer Friendly Version with Opt-Out Form

**Please note:**   
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
---|---  
  
###### Questions?

| 

Call toll-free 1-800-924-4427  
  
###### WHO WE ARE

|   
---|---  
  
###### Who is providing this notice?

| 

First United means the following institutions: First United Bank and Trust Company and First United Bank Insurance Solutions, Inc.  
  
###### WHAT WE DO

|   
  
###### How does First United protect my personal information?

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.  
  
###### How does First United collect my personal information?

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

  * open an account or use your credit or debit card
  * apply for a loan or apply for insurance
  * tell us about your investment or retirement portfolio

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
###### Why can't I limit all sharing?

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

  * Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
###### What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?

| 

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.  
  
###### DEFINITIONS

|   
---|---  
  
###### Affiliates

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.

  * Our affiliates include
  * Financial companies such as: First United Bank Insurance Solutions, Inc.

###### Nonaffiliates

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.

  * First United does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.

###### Joint Marketing

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * Our joint marketing partners include Insurance Companies.

###   
Online Privacy Policy

Printer Friendly Version

**FIRST UNITED BANK - ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY**

This Online privacy policy governs the manner in which First United Bank collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.firstunitedbank.com website ("Site"). This online privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered through the Site by First United Bank.

**Personal identification information**   
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, or phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**   
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**   
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. A User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. A User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, they should note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**   
First United Bank may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
• To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
• To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
• To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
• To process applications  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when applying for a product or service. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.  
• To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
• To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include a link to unsubscribe or instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**   
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**   
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**   
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Google AdWords remarketing**   
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the First United Bank’s Website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page.

**Changes to this online privacy policy**   
First United Bank has the discretion to update this online privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this online privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**   
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**   
If you have any questions about this online privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
First United Bank   
https://www.firstunitedbank.com  
1400 West Main Street, Durant, Oklahoma 74701   
Mailing Address: P.O. Box 130, Durant, OK 74702  
580-924-2211 or 800-924-4427  
fubinfo@firstunitedbank.com

This document was last updated on August 1, 2015.

### Social Media Policy

If you have a customer service question, please contact us at 1-800-924-4427 or email us at fubinfo@firstunitedbank.com during business hours. Please do not include your Social Security Number, account number or request financial information or transactions when contacting us online. 

Moderation of First United Bank's Social Media pages will be conducted on an ongoing basis.

We encourage your participation, comments, shares and likes on our pages and ask that you respect others who participate here.

We may remove comments that don't respect the discussion or its participants, contain spam, sensitive personal information, inappropriate links, threatening, defamatory, profane, obscene or abusive material, or ones that suggest illegal activity.

We do not endorse third-party links that appear on this site. Also, comments posted do not represent the opinions of First United Bank. 

We may use or share the comments you make on our Facebook wall, which gives us the ability to share your stories and comments.

Facebook and other social media platforms are owned and operated by a third party not affiliated with First United Bank. 

This is a public forum. Please do not post sensitive personal or financial information.  
You participate at your own risk, taking personal responsibility for your comments, your username and any information provided.

This document was last updated on June 16, 2016.
